Hello, I
Need to push my PC back under my desk. It's too loud. I could hear it. Oh my god. Shut up
It's because I was exporting something in from here anyways, sorry. Thank you for waiting everybody. Hello. Welcome to
Super Sunday. Hold on. Let me fix one thing
Baba bot should be live, right? I hope
Baba bot is live, right?
Super Sunday. Hello everybody. Thank you guys so much for the super chat. So yeah, this uh
This stream is a Sunday. You guys know
dedicated to rating super chats
Yeah, good to see you guys again. Am I I feel like uh, hold on one second
Hi, my head's small, okay, this is better wait, not really
That looks normal sort of maybe a little bit bigger
It looks
somewhat normal, okay
My immersion, oh no, oh you'll live you'll live
Oh
Man I was gonna bring berries
I was gonna bring berries to the stream. I had blackberries and I left them in the kitchen
Well, I get them later. Yes, uh, Baba is already on although there's no song requests open
I'm gonna open up the song cue now
Give me one a moment
How can you add songs great question
well
you would do exclamation point SR which stands for song request and then put the link of the song you would like to request in
in the chat of Bubba, but
Which I don't remember the
Command is it working? Oh
Hold on, let me check something really quick one sec
You
Okay, now Bubba about his playing can you guys hear it sorry I had to hold on
Okay
Okay, yeah, it's loud okay, I'll turn down a little bit
Okay, turn it down is that better
You can hear now, okay cool. So yeah, the key is already open and it fills up really fast because you guys are like
robots
Just on top of it. So it's likely that the queue is already filled. Mm-hmm
Now I don't know if we're gonna finish the queue this stream because the stream will probably be I don't know
I was assuming it would be wouldn't be that long of a stream. So we'll see. Mm-hmm
Yeah lately lately my energy has been really low even though I try not to show it on stream
But it's kind of just like waking up is uh, sometimes just like oh getting out of bed
And I think it's cuz I keep ordering out no more ordering out
So today I had a delicious breakfast of leftover rice and oh some seaweed that like I got in the tub
It's like the seaweed salad and eggs and some leftover cauliflower
Mm-hmm
Yeah, cuz even my my my my nails like break super easily. They're like really brittle
So I think it's just a nutrients thing. So I've been really low on energy. So these streams probably
I'll try to go for as long as I can but I don't know for until it until I recover
Yeah, the streams might be just a little short yeah, I take vitamins I take a gummy bear vitamins
They're pretty good. I think I
Can't eat two of them. It's better than just eating one. It's like a Flintstone gummy. Yeah, I
Think it might switch to the office. I mean we're in the office, but I mean it might go to my desk instead
Hold on. Oh, yeah, I put it like a
It puts some crazy filters on my office trying to make it 3d. Hold on. Let me tell you
Where is it, um
Let's see
Okay
Weird hold on let me cut there for a second
Oh
Where is it maybe if I do there's music playing, huh?
Disappeared
The office is gone
Doesn't make any sense
Don't make no sense. Wait
There's that
It's probably just like an OBS problem
Oh
What if I duplicate
All same issue, maybe I just have too many things on this. Oh
Those dreams I think sorry. Okay, I guess we'll stay here
Yeah, I tried to check earlier, but I guess cuz I was trying to do I was trying to put the office
I was trying to make it like give it this cool 3d effect
We're like, you know how you look at something with the red and blue glasses. Oh
And it's like it looks 3d
Yeah, I was gonna do that. Well, let me check something else
Are you guys doing today on this Sunday? Oh
That's better now it doesn't look like I'm reading although my arms look so big
Good
Does that work
Is it I think it's just too big in general
Immersion chillin at bed nice hungry get a snack
That's a little bit better maybe just a tiny bit
Wait, is this is this lined up this where is this supposed to be? Oh here looks so high
Okay, well what it looks scuff to me wait, okay, I just don't look don't look don't look don't look
What happened to Papa but is it playing cuz I don't hear anything
Is it just a really quiet song is there just like a minute of silence at the end of a song or something
It stopped it broke
But it only lets me play this one song. Well, then let me reload it really quick
Okay, hopefully that fixed it. Yeah, I guess it has to be this way. Very funny. Very funny. Yeah
Shoot
I'm trying to hide this misaligned pillow. Oh, what is this? Maybe if I
Look the pillow has like a little bite taken out of it. I think it's supposed to go by this armrest, but it don't fit
So I'm a lid I won't fit
Okay, we'll say that that's don't look oh my god don't look what this is confusing
Okay, we'll just we'll just say this is how wait, I get it I get it I get it
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Does this look normal to you guys? I honestly can't tell anymore. Okay, whatever. It's fine
All right, so we have all gathered here today
To give thanks for thy super chats
Uh
Wait, does anybody know where from where I'm reading from super chat's from my head is too big
Oh
Hey pecs, well, okay, you guys are so useful. Thank you
Yeah, I don't know what's wrong with me lately, it's like my brains been so blank
Like I went to the fish store to buy the frogs and I was like talking to the lady. We're like talking about
Oh
You know coolly loaches that wanted to add to my tank and stuff and then afterwards after I got the frogs
I was just like oh my god. I'm so tired. What the heck. It's so mentally draining just to
Just to like go outside and talk
with person at the store
But I think it'll get better yeah, it'll get better I'll still try to still trying to stream
I've been getting enough sleep. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I've been getting enough sleep. I
Think it's just especially cuz I was traveling a few weeks ago, and I've been ordering out a lot. I think it's just
Not healthy for my tummy. Oh
What day was the apex tree well then let me look at the schedule
Oh
Speaking of the schedule I kind of have it lined up
For the next
The next coming this coming week, let's see
I will tell you guys but first let me see what day that effects was
Oh wasn't that on Monday? When it was not on Monday
Wait, yes, it was a Monday
No
It was on Tuesday
Okay, okay
Sorry, sorry
Okay, so I'll tell you guys the schedule
sort of
Yeah, the loose schedule for this week. Well, not sort of I'm gonna try to stick to it tomorrow. We'll play Elden ring
starting at AMT time and
Then on Tuesday, I didn't really plan out this day because we're doing the Mario Kart this day, I think
So I think it's it's gonna be at the same time. We scheduled that or it might be a little bit earlier
So that'd be Mario Kart collab that we had to reschedule last week
Um, and then I don't know what I'm gonna do a Tuesday night. I'm not sure yet
If I do anything and then on Wednesday, we have a member stream
I looked at the list and I remember one of the things I said was the horror stream
So there was a horror game that we can do for members. I don't know if I don't know
I don't know if it's a good game, but I guess we'll find out and
Then also that night I will probably play more Elden ring
I might switch it out for something else though and then on Thursday. Um, I have rust here with a question mark
So I'm not sure
If it's gonna be on that day
But I might just try to play rust on that day. Oh, I don't have anything else planned for that day. Oh
Then on Friday
What does this music stop to get? It doesn't let me play the next one
Keep having to refresh it every time
Hold on. Let me check. Let me refresh for real. I'll get us restart the bubble box stream. I think it's being really lame right now
I
Okay, hopefully I fix it you guys here Bubba, okay. Yeah bubbles barking at something
That's cuz yeah bubba bubba what the heck bubba you're supposed to be DJing
All right, and then on Friday, I don't have anything planned I'm not sure yet and then on Saturday
We'll watch spider-man 2 and then I thought we could do the wheel stream again
Probably get a few different games, you know, maybe some
Minecraft or something and then super Sunday. See I'm still in the middle of planning it
Is that like a bird an alarm
Alright super chats from
Five days ago got it. Oh
But before we read super chat, she's gonna see look look look wait
Oh
Look at this wait, it's too big
Hold on oh
It's gone and disappeared what the heck
Oh
It's gone oh
Alright hold on I have to manually shrink it. Oh, yes, everything is being weird today
Look at the starfish
Let me restart from the beginning. I found I these are starfish that I've seen on the rocks in my tank
But now I got it on the I got I found it on the glass and I could zoom in and get a close-up of it
Obviously the starfish is missing one leg. I think it did it on purpose
to reproduce or whatever because I've seen like other starfish that was only it only had like two legs, so
Yeah, so this is in real time it crawling like across the glass
It's cute, right?
You can see the mouth in the center there
Or is it the butthole? I don't know that much about starfish anatomy
Yeah, they got those little feelers that they use to crawl across the
You know the land
The little feet which are also tongues I think and we started to
Yeah, both it's both weird
Yeah, it's so cute. It's so small
so small and then also
Right now, where did it go? Oh, it's so small
This is real time. Hold on. I want to pause it because it goes by fast. This is a new anemone that I bought
It's um
Can I use the point?
It's uh, let me see. I must have something to point with I need a pointer
like a little cursor to drag around the screen
Alright, I'll point with
This my detached arm this right here. This is a really small anemone
I think it's a bubble tip anemone. Yeah, I was at the fish store and
the guy at the fish store was I was like buying my stuff and
Then I was like, oh, what's that thing on the glass?
it's
Okay, the video was unavailable
Anyways, I was like, what is that thing on the glass and he was like, oh, it's just a little one of my nominees that cloned
I'll sell it to you for ten bucks and I was like, oh
Well since you're offering okay, I got it for ten bucks and let's sit your baby you can see how small it is
It's the same size as a small hermit crab. So it's really small and I saw them together again this morning
They were like together the whole night and they formed a symbiotic relationship because what happens is that the hermit crab
Yeah, they form a symbiotic relationship with the anemone because the anemone will sting
things that might try to catch the hermit crab like octopus or squid and
In return the hermit crab eats its food and shares the little bits that fall off with the anemone
So they have like a really cute relationship
Anyways, this video that I took is um, I had just turned on the light to check on it on them
Um, and this is the anemone opening up in real time. Mm-hmm
Now you could see it
It's like a it's like a flower opening up so it's not sped up or anything
This is how it opens up in real time. And then when it closes, it looks really cute, too
Look, they're holding hands right there. Where did I see? He's touching it
Yeah, they're very cute and it has this anemone has such a pretty color
Although I was I didn't think about it to be honest when I bought it
But uh, I was after I bought it I got really worried. I was like, oh, what if I do actually have a bobbit worm
So I've been keeping an eye on the tank like at night. Um, I haven't I don't know
I've never really seen any signs of a bobbit worm other than one of the the only fish that I had in tank disappearing
So, I don't know. I mean Mogu was skinny and
Stressed out so it couldn't it's it's not guaranteed that there was a bobbit worm
But apparently they do try to eat anemones. So I guess we'll see I'll try to keep a close eye on it
I want to protect it
Yeah, this a anemone
It's moved. It's it's moved up a little bit on this rock and yeah, I found them together again this morning. So cute
They're so cute. And then
And then let me see, hold on
Hold on
Hold on, hold on, I guess it's too zoomed in
Okay, now I will show you guys
The frog
After I change something really quick
Um
This one
Okay, I use this image watch as I transform this arm
You frog
Yeah, why is it so so big? Oh shoot. Okay. Hold on. I messed it up
All that, I'm shrinking the image. Oh when I take a picture, it's like 400,000 pixels
There's one of the frogs
Um, kind of floating. Yeah, floating and um
He wasn't always floating he was just doing it to get air so they stayed in the tank in the water
They're fully aquatic, but they actually go up to the surface to get air
And so he was just like going up to the surface to get some air
Yeah, African dwarf frog. I got two of them. I don't have a picture of both of them together
But let me see
No, this is the only picture I have actually
Yeah, this is the frog I fed them again
Um, I fed them like as soon as I added them into the tank because they seemed kind of hungry and then I fed them
Again this morning. Well, I only fed one of them this morning because it was really skinny
Are they both males? I don't know. I guess we'll find out
Um, they seem to be chilling though. The tank's really long. So they have a lot of space
Yeah, we'll see
Look at them. I need to zoom in
Are they gonna make tadpoles? I don't know. I think if they did make tadpoles probably my fish would eat them
But yeah for my freshwater tank. I want to get some freshwater clams
Seems cute
What do they eat? I feed them bloodworms, but they also eat like pellets
They'll eat flakes if you like hold it right in front of their face
They'll pretty much eat anything that you hold in front of their face because I was trying to feed one this morning
And it was eating the sand because it kept like trying to go for the worm and it kept missing
So it was getting a mouthful of sand
Oh, but it did spit it out. It didn't actually eat it
No, they don't usually bother shrimp
Not that I've seen anyway
I guess it's possible they could eat something. They'll eat like whatever fits in their mouth
But they're also really really blind. So I don't think they'll be able to eat anything
I
Everything's always so good. Well, there's so many red super chats at the top of the chat today. Thank you guys
Okay, now I will for real start reading super chats and probably get distracted
But it doesn't look like we have too much to go
I didn't have to scroll too much to get down to these super chats now reading from the apex collab with a mume
I am ego. Thank you. We're gonna come times to thank you discuss the Batman. Thank you
Maffy, thank you. Oh
Right here. Thank you
Well, check is going in the care package. Why people don't even use it, right? What the heck?
I can of course die. Thank you a quick. Thank you
Rip boats in not the boats in not the boats in just a boat. Check a slow champ. Thank you. I skip it. Thank you
Of course that day. Thank you. I'm a cemented
Thank you. I'm smart boy. Thank you
worthless old crinkle
Thank you
but
Thank you. Yeah, I don't think we got one win that whole time we played, huh?
Fine I get wins off off
stream
Like the one time I played apex off
Me for me to say thank you. Can we get 99? Thank you a new tube crashed. Thank you. Oh
Kitty stamps. Thank you
I'm right. Thank you. Number one victory for you. Well, then I got a reopen chat
Red Juliet, thank you pick a break. Oh
Thank you. Yeah, I'm not that great at apex. I think I think I might be better at fortnight. Actually, I don't know. Yeah
I'm not that good at FPS games. I think I have my moments in like FPS games
But overall I don't think I'm that great of a player. I just have really good
I've like I have times where I'm really focused in and I actually do well
Then most of the time I just get distracted like I start reading chat and then I start following my teammates
They start messing around in the game
Yeah, it's it's well
It's distracting streaming and playing at the same time because you know, there's so much all these people in chat. I could talk to
Mm-hmm
Joshua Bernardo, thank you
Well, thank you, thank you a finger I think yep
Tk. Thank you. Wait Jesse ready? Thank you. Oh
George dedicated accounts. Thank you. Yeah, we're probably play more apex this week because I'm gonna do a wheel stream
So I think apex. Oh, yeah, do I have I should pin that wheel? Hold on do I saw if I go to the wheel?
wheel website
Let me see if everything's still there it is it is oh my god if I were playing it now I would get
hold on it's spinning if
I if I were playing the wheel now, we'd be playing heroes of the storm
Now members camp over wheel games I put stuff on the wheel that I feel like I wouldn't mind playing
Thank you
Yeah, here's the soul well, we'll have to see on the day the day of wheel
They have wheel ah speaking of which yeah, I'll do it after the stream for sure wait
No, I was gonna say it. Let me set this twitch vod to download. Hold on. Let me put this on my
bookmarks bookmarked
Why are so many things open I'll close that at that
Close it at that. Okay
I pick a wreck. Thank you Aaron Pompo. Thank you. I don't know anything. Yep. Oh Lord turn up. Thank you
95% of gamblers quit right before they hit it big
Yeah, yeah. Yeah
That's a that's a cop if I've ever heard one
I'm Fred. Thanks so much for the 100 big
super chat
Not a name. I've heard before
I'm reading super chat. So thank you so much for support
Bonsie, thank you
Well, the thing is yes as you should turn you should turn back on the screen when playing apex as you're about to land
So then nobody can follow you but it's difficult because if I'm the jump master
I have to be tapped into the game to
Well, I could put it on a hotkey
Yeah, I could put it on a hockey like uh, I
Guess it would be like this. Hold on. Let me see I can show you guys a demonstration if you will
Like that it would be just like that. Yeah, I'll put it on a hockey. That's a good idea. Thanks. I'm it
Okay, 360 monkey. Thank you
Get in times to thank you reindeer. Thank you a worthless old crinkle. Oh
Thank you
Rick. Thank you
Yeah, the readers are good. Well, I don't know it depends
I only want to eat like a Dorito maybe like once every six months or something. I don't know
I don't really have cravings for chips
Yeah
It's a lessons. Thank you
And new a sign I got dog
Can you stay I was a thank you. I shoot a sucky. Thank you gentlemen
Thank you. Oh, yeah, I learned something today
Well, it was like while I was reading
researching some stuff
Apparently if you guys look at your nails right now
Do you guys have like a little white half moon at the bottom part of your nail where it like connects to your finger?
Do you guys have that check check?
everybody check
Yes, yes, yep, nope. No. Yes. Yes
Yeah, it's called the wait. I forget what it's called Luna lei. I think Luna lei
Uh-huh. Yeah, it means yet. It means if you're missing it, it might mean that you have
issues with like nutrition or vitamins
Uh-huh. Wait, let me look up the right name
Yeah, it's called a Luna lei
Luna lei, it's the crescent shaped whitish area of the bed of a nail or toenail and
And if you don't have it, it might indicate some underlying conditions
It's possible that it could mm-hmm. Well, that's what it says on the internet anyways
But I'm sure there's probably like some studies that proved it wrong or something
That's good. Yeah, it's good if you have one. I don't have any I
Don't have any no you won't I wait do I have any looking at my toenails, right? I have one on my big toe
Oh
That's good, maybe my I guess my feet are healthier
Yeah, yeah looking at look up it's like when you can tell what color it's like the color of stuff that comes out of your
Body indicates, you know like things in your body, right?
Yeah, I'm all nervous from lack of I'm a
Okay, okay. Oh, yeah, I like this song nice. Okay. Oh, where was I reading super chats back to super chats?
Pick a right thing here. Oh, that would be cool. I need toe. Thank you. It is named on sites with fuse old for six times
zoom, oh
I want to play more fuse
Is the season starting again soon on apex? Maybe I'll give it the good old try
I'll try hard
We'll see I
Was like just getting out of silver or just getting out of bronze it
It's such a huge time sink. I feel like climbing ranks in CS go is probably easier or like an overwatch
It takes less time. Well, I don't know
I guess if you're winning every single game if you're getting like 200 RP every single game in apex
Maybe it's not that much time
But maybe because I spend a lot of time in games where I get like 60 RP or something and then we die
Seems yeah, it seems really grindy though
Hmm
Mm-hmm. There's a new rank. So it makes it harder. Oh, oh right. Yeah, cuz they have like the new brink or something
Rookie that's what it is. I guess it would be insulting if they called it noob
Hmm it seems satisfying, you know get up there. Oh
Okay
Sorry, I have this like leftover
Skin bubble from a blister. I just felt that you
You
Okay
Our name was Oda
Okay, uh
What was I
What'd you do? Thank you. I don't like thank you. I lost saying room. Thank you. Good to be
Good. Yeah, so you say you cover with nami mamos absolute fire. Oh, thank you. I'm glad you liked it. I
Just cuz the Batman. Thank you. I'll fall in walls
Thank you so much, I appreciate the support
But the button
Oh, oh, oh, oh multi. Thank you
I'm done source. Thank you. Just in time. Thank you. I can't thank you. Thank you. Thank you
What's three four five? Thank you. My June 8th
Thank you not blue. Thank you. I have wing. Thank you. Nice boat
Thank you
salad
Mass man today. Thank you. Yo, yo, yo, yo, or yeah. Yo, yo, yo, yo
Slow champ. Thank you. It's possible to get duplicator and yet server and we're grinding just fun building
I don't think so
cuz uh
Thanks, somebody might have been trying to build like some sort of farm that required building
and like the ceiling of the nether something and
Yeah, we're it's not allowed and stuff. So I don't think we can take advantage of things like that. Uh-huh
Okay now reading super chats from
Oh a four night collab
It ain't didn't didn't think
Maybe it is possible. I don't know. I
Maybe I read it wrong
Oh my god, yay for that. Oh my god. We like for night. Mm-hmm
All right, I couldn't thank you
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. I'll pick correct. Thank you
Oh, yeah, I have a I have a cool skin import night
So I'm pretty sure that's what makes me better than everybody else and the game
That's a little champ. Oh, thank you. Oh very good. Good. Thank you. I have wing. Thank you
Thank you. Thank you. Yes, there's no BGM because we are listening to BGM on Boba bot radio
Pick a work they wait. Thank you
Didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't
Thank you. Thank you. Can I stay up staying cute? Oh
Just in time, thank you. Yeah, what's the spot to drop in a fortnight tomato town Lake?
Do they ever have a new fortnight map or do they just add stuff to it?
Oh cute
Oh, I like the horns
Oh
Oh, we live off just in time. Thank you and to be saying cute banana hollow. That'd be cute
I'm smart boy. Thank you
Oh, thank you
Quick thank you
All right. Thank you. Please don't wipe out tomato town. I should make that a priority. Actually the next time I play Fortnite
We're gonna wipe out tomato town
Goody Sam. Thank you
We're gonna give their season 8 battle pass out for free. Oh
Oh that because they were worried about apex. Oh
interesting
Oh
Girl cube. Thank you
Yesterday come some it up
Good morning four days ago
Okay
Mads man, thank you
Oh really like the horns is so cute
Good
Faster faster
Oh
Into fish, thank you
I
Has little brother Watson giving you any pro Fortnite tips
No, but I did I did watch them while they were playing and they did get a win which actually that's why I wanted to
play Fortnite because uh
Yeah, watching watching the Watson brothers play
I was kind of
Kind of uh, made me want to play too
Thank you
What do you mean it's the original ship you got to go with the original one, you know what the what the creator originally intended
Which is a definitely Naruto and Sasuke
Good stamps. Thank you
Thank you
Uh
I can't say I'm saying here. Oh, thank you. Thank you. I'm a dungeon
Uh, thank you
Uh
Kitty stamps, thank you. I want to add my ice cream with dumbbell eyes
Oh, that would be cool
What if you guys saw like a uh crunchy roll expo kyara got like her
Her little kfp stand selling real food
It's actually funny like well watching her help plan for it because it's like she really became
a fast food chain
like
owner, you know
So um
Yeah, it's cool. It's cool that that happened. Yeah at a crunch roll expo you could get um some kfp food. Uh-huh
So who knows maybe in the future we can have an ami popsicle
Yeah, I think there were pictures online right apparently it was like super sold out
Out like they even had to take an item off the menu because it sold out really fast
The sliders are good. Oh, you guys are supposed to be hungry
All convention food is over price you should know that if you're getting in line
It's because it's because they can so they will
Uh ticket thank you
Thank you, oh the battle bus yeah, it's just zero trucks him
Uh, can you say i'm saying here a super chat and vbucks i'll take it. This is like what not even a hundred vbucks
All right. All right
Book a week. Thank you
Um, yeah, it's really funny because I wasn't sure because I have two like accounts for fortnite. I guess unintentionally
Um, and I wasn't sure which account had the you know the skin
And so I I was like asking, you know
Because I had 100 vbucks in one account and then I had 550 vbucks in the other account
And I was like, oh maybe just on one account you start with like 100 vbucks or something or I earned that
So I was like, you know, do you have any vbucks?
It's funny it made yeah, it sounds like a mom. I want vbucks. Give me vbucks
Unironically though, that is what a little brother watson got for christmas
some vbucks from uh older brother watson
Um, amela what's up defective extraordinaire. Thank you. What brother watson's 19 fortnite
Uh, i'm pretty sure I would still win if I'm controller, it would be easy probably here sam. Thank you
You get back bling for free. Oh if you buy among us on the epic store you get the backpack in fortnite. Wow
Wow, that sounds like an offer. I just can't pass up. I do have to buy among us though, which is weird. I thought I had it
Jada wise. Thank you
Well, thank you, uh, can you stand stay thank you
uh
Okay, this is not the real guard. Good. It's just somebody who
Pretend to be her
No, thank you
Amigo. Thank you
Um
Oh, thank you. Yeah fortnite is. All right, sometimes I guess
It can be pretty fun. I guess
And much do you think yep
Uh, just see the happy guy. Thank you
Gold name means they have a victory crown if you pick one up and get a victory royale
It's supposed to be better than a regular royale
Huh
I don't know what this means
I see
I can't stay. I'm saying cute
Oh
Psycho, thank you. Can you stay. I'm so thank you
I messed with you. Thank you a bus. Thank you
All right, we're now reading super chats from euro truck sim and then super chats from this stream
And then that'll be all the super chats
And then we'll take a break and then i'll be back with sam's studies. Oh wait, it's not sims. Hey skylight. Sorry
Oh
Euro truck sam
I was talking about kfp for chicken sounds good
Oh, yeah city skyline that sim city city skyline, uh-huh
Actually, I still have to buy it and download it now, but it should be really fast I think
Thank
Oh work out good. Thank you. I discussed about man. Thank you
small mommy is definitely british
I'll ask a paycheck as much for the
You
Okay
Test it fuck
Test test
Sorry, it's because I have it saved. Oh my god, it's so loud. Sorry
There's like different mic profiles in the go xlr, uh
In the go xlr thingy a program
And uh, every time I reset the program it keeps singing that I have my mic
You
Test
Test test
Test test test test test test test test test test
Test.
Music?
What, can you guys hear it?
No, you can't, right?
Music?
No.
You guys didn't hear anything.
Okay, it's only for a second.
Yeah, we'll be fine.
Test.
Okay, does it sound better now?
Okay.
I think there's just some weird discrepancy
between the hardware and the software.
Wait, does it work now?
Super Chat!
Thank you!
Okay, I think it's because I had my PC on,
but sometimes I like disconnect the GoXLR or something.
Or, Henry disconnects it.
Okay.
I'm gonna fix something.
Test.
No, no, no, no, no.
Take me to the eye of your mind.
Don't you know you might find a better place to play?
Okay.
I'm smart boy, thank you.
Small Amet earned her trucking license fair and square.
Very good, thank you.
I could be gonna know, thank you.
Hey, she said the things I had went to my head.
I've been back with someone down in New York.
Stand up beside the bonfire,
and then look from up your face.
You ain't ever going to burn my heart out.
Thank you, but correct, thank you.
Small Amet caused a multitude of accidents
on that fateful day.
What is that, thank you.
Tenet, thank you.
A stratify, thank you.
Did you ever watch World Star Bites?
Oh, is that like where you go, oh World Star, World Star.
I've seen a few of those.
Oh, isn't there like really messed up stuff though, too?
Amet, thank you.
Oh, thank you for your dedication, Amet, thank you.
Nobody knows if it's night or day.
Oh, wow.
Mess me up, thank you.
This is the start of revolution from my bed.
Cause she said the things I had went to my head.
Small Amet's gonna drive a truck,
she's too small to see through the windshield.
Yes, yes, no, Small Amet had a booster seat.
Yeah, it was okay.
Take that look from off your face.
See, you ain't ever gonna burn my heart out.
And some girl we can't wait.
She knows it's too late.
Well, yeah, go to side, oh, thank you.
Thank you, Small Amet, cause you reached the pedal.
I think she had some sort of set up where she had like a peg
leg kind of strapped to one of her legs.
A pickle rig, thank you.
Instead of please step on me, Amet,
please run me over, Small Amet.
Yeah, must yes, thank you.
I'm sorry, it'd be an honor to be is a kind by these Small Amet.
All right, dear, thank you.
Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da,
do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
So Kelly can wait.
She knows it's too late as we're walking on by.
Her soul slides away.
And I'll look back and I'll go back to say.
Slow Tam, thank you, the Isekai Express, whoa, whoa.
Half wing, thank you.
Delorean truck, cool.
Bus, thank you.
Did you order some of the Omoket and Council Iris merch?
Which ones would you get?
I did, I got the main one.
And I think I got Mumei's,
because I liked how kind of subtle it was.
And then also Fauna's sweater.
And, oh, that was cool.
I get it for free.
I don't order Mumei's birthday merch.
I think I'm, I think I'm done ordering people's merch,
because I always forget.
It always, well, I get like a ton of emails
from before the haul.
Does that still happen with the Hololive shop
where if you order merch, like it gives you an email
and it's like, it's at a warehouse.
Please pay, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I'm just like, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Yeah, Fauna's sweater is so cute.
Not from the official store.
Okay, because I have a ton of stuff that I got from Byee
and it was, well, they have extras now, I guess.
I mean, it's still mine, it's so, you know,
I just like supported them, I guess.
I just never got the item.
Ah, ah, ah.
Magic, magic.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, is this a sign, you guys want me to sing this song
for karaoke?
Magic.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
It's magic, magic.
I can't read, it's too small.
All I have to do is think of you
to make the music start to play.
Then I dance from down the street and I'm, I can't read.
Hey, hey, hey, magic ways.
Ooh, you love the girl with magic ways.
And it's true.
Oh, I can't read, it's too small.
The text is too small, I'm struggling here.
Okay.
Night and night and oh, sweet magic ways.
Oh, where was I?
Oh, Ricardo, thank you.
Oh, Reginald, thank you.
Oh, I want to translate this one.
Magic, magic.
Thank you, thank you, thank you profile, so cute.
Must be my new YouTube, I want to say Yo YouTube.
My new YouTube profile picture, thank you.
I think that it was the, well,
I was just like looking through Pixel
and I was trying so many different pictures
and like it's just that, you know,
having blonde hair and being super pale,
it's kind of hard with contrast,
like to find a good image that contrasts properly
for like a small profile picture.
So I was just Googling my name
and looking through the images and I found this one
and I'm pretty sure this is like one of the first images
I tweeted, like right after our debut announcement.
So I just tried it and it actually didn't look so bad.
So I decided to keep it.
Magic, magic.
Oh, right dude, thank you.
Yuste, kam samita.
I ate Amaz menu at a collaboration cafe yesterday.
It was really good.
Hope there'll be more events like this next time.
Oh, thank you, kam samita, kam amo yo.
Yeah, about the cafe in Korea.
And yeah, I saw like what Kyara shared,
like some pictures of some very dedicated
Hello Live fans camping out just to get into the cafe,
like camping out like 12 hours or something before it opens.
I think they were camping out like at midnight,
waiting for it to open
because there's not a lot of spots in the cafe.
So take some dedication, you know.
It's just, no one was expecting such a large turnout
for the cafe, so thank you, kam samita.
Yeah, they're very dedicated
and they seem really happy too.
I'd love for everybody to be able to go to cafe like that.
It'd be awesome.
Well, not one where you have to wait, you know, so long,
but still.
Yeah, that's true.
They keep underestimating us.
When will they learn?
Psycho, thank you.
Oh, some coins, thank you.
Pick a ring, thank you.
Oh yeah, I saw.
Was there like for real GTA six announcement?
Or was it like a leak or something?
I'm ending things, I know.
Oh, it's real.
They're working on it.
Didn't it take like 10 years for GTA five
or some like really long amount?
Yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup, yup.
Cool, I definitely played GTA six
when it comes out in four years.
Storm blade, thank you.
I believe Smulama did isekai some people on that.
Faithful day.
Storm, oh wait, right next, thank you.
YouTube crashed again, thank you.
I'm gonna get a close chat.
All right.
Where was I?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Thank you, the song is distracting.
TK, thank you.
Can you say I'm saying thank you?
Reindeer, thank you.
I'm a reed.
Thank you, some, oh, attack a goalie, thank you.
I almost said Smulama.
Yeah, investigators meeting, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Thank you for the support.
I didn't go, we didn't go, thank you.
Are we there yet?
I have to use the bathroom.
Bubba hit me, it's too hot.
Can we get McDonald's over there yet?
Shut up.
Aw, cute.
A new song, arigato.
Yejun, thank you.
Last time someone drew a picture of Smulama standing outside the big truck
fighting a piece of wheat straw,
does Smulama want to find someone's mother again?
Smulama's got a whole phone book,
whole of, uh, you know,
you know, uh, victims, nah, nah, nah.
Friends.
Smulama's got a lot of friends.
Or to the, thank you.
Thank you.
Halfwayang, thank you.
Yeah, GTA 5, the Europe map DLC.
Can I say I'm saying cute?
Taro Cube, saying cute.
Maybe trucker Smulama's license from the wrong timeline.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, it's not very valid here.
Airbumble, thank you.
Pickle Rick times two, thank you.
Boss music in Eurotrucks.
I guess there was as we were parking.
We have a day, thank you.
I'm glad you enjoyed the stream, thank you.
Thank you.
Yeah, everybody left the factory,
the carrot factory as Smulama was trying to deliver.
I guess it would be the, I don't know, processing plant maybe.
Uh-huh.
Damn, you could fit a lot of carrots in like a 22-foot long truck, huh?
Like tons and tons of carrots.
Whoa.
Okay, thank you.
This is harder than me landing on a sun station or parking a truck.
The sun station took way longer.
Mila, what's up, Detective Extraordinaire, thank you.
Hey, Solasos, thank you.
Wouldn't it be cool if truck sim had a Fallout mod?
It sounds very specific.
I guess it'd be more believable if Fallout had a truck sim mod.
Uh, Amadeus, thank you.
Hidezuki, thank you.
By color, thank you.
Up a creek, thank you.
Yeah, I'll just get a real truck and see how it is, how it really is.
Uh, Dunlides, thank you.
Uh, Slotham, thank you.
Nice boat, thank you.
Isute, Kamsamita.
Wait, is this what it says? Let me double check.
Okay, Multi, thank you.
Wajaleo, thank you.
Twilight, thank you.
Fishstar, thank you.
Alright, only about 20% left of the superchets, including the ones from the stream.
Itchy.
Hold on.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's a guy's simulator, I like that.
Uh, Rekukun, thank you.
Um, A screen, thank you.
Truckson.
Can I say it? So thank you.
Thank you for watching.
Kamsamita.
Jiho, komawa yo.
Mayscreen, thank you.
Aw, thank you.
Kuristai, thank you.
Alright, now superchets from two days ago. What did we do two days ago?
Oh, wait, is this from the free chat? Oh, no.
Okay, I guess there's some from the free chat and then some from the today stream.
Kuristai, thank you.
Oh, Rekukun, thank you.
I'm at Crunchyroll Expo for the next two days.
I'll be the vlogging. Oh, nice.
Did I stream? I don't remember.
Just in time, thank you.
I hope you enjoyed the convention.
Oh, karaoke.
Rekukun, thank you.
Oh, oh, yes.
It was really cool. I don't know if it was in the stream,
but like during when Gura was singing, like on my end,
I was getting like fade in and fade out of like the crowd,
close up of like the crowd with their light sticks and it looked like a real concert
and it was so cool, such a cool moment, even though it's really short
because Gura only sang like the first verse in the chorus for Shiny Smiley Story.
Aw, so was it on the stream, like the crowd waving their glow sticks and stuff?
Aw, cool.
Yeah, it was really cool.
I'm glad she agreed because I think she's busy like recording,
so her voice was not that great.
She didn't have a lot of sleep in the first place,
so I'm glad I'm gonna, I hope it wasn't too much pressure,
but yeah, it was a really cool moment to see Gura like,
it's so magic when she sings, you know what I mean?
And seeing like everybody's live reaction to it too.
It's so cool.
Mm-hmm, so magical.
Aw, where was I?
Aw, I made me a thank you.
How was it to meet some of your fans?
I think it was cool, I don't know, maybe I was not that great at conversation,
so I was just like, there'd be like a kind of a pause and I'd say,
well, how was your convention going?
Did you see the KFP stand?
I had some topics, you know, did you buy anything today?
Did you see the Artist Alley?
How many did I meet?
I think, I don't know the exact number,
but I know it was supposed to be like around 20 or so.
I think a little bit more than 20.
Aw, okay, good, thank you.
I was one of the Santiago cosplayers, oh cool.
Good, it's a bad influence.
Good, I didn't mention feet at all at first.
It was just some guy in the crowd.
Ms. Mint, thank you.
Yeah, we made a thank you.
Can I ask about the coin purse?
It's super cute and I want one.
I think I want it from an arcade or something at some point,
like a long time ago.
Oh yeah, just so you can put coins and stuff in it.
Pickle Rick, thank you.
Next meeting greets, yeah.
I wouldn't mind doing them as often.
This is convention season still right now,
but during convention season I don't mind doing it.
It only took like two hours, but it was pretty fun.
I think doing the panel was more difficult
than doing the meeting greets because,
well, usually in the past when we do panels,
there's somebody, you know, there's like an MC
who deals with handling the crowd
and asking questions and things like that
and just keeping the flow going for the panel,
but because it was up to each of us,
Good and I were talking about different ideas
that we could do for the panel,
and we just didn't come to a conclusion
of what it is we should do because we had some ideas.
I think one was doing a live AI dungeon session or something,
and I was like, oh, we could look at funny animal videos.
So we had a lot of ideas,
but we ended up just going with like what staff recommended,
like, oh, just, you know, questions.
MeTuber support, okay.
It was easy.
And then, yeah, everybody had like six in the crowd,
so I really wanted to, you know,
work with that too and do a little musical thing.
Yeah, well, I had an idea to do like a 3D panel.
I was gonna, well, first I wanted to see how feasible it was.
If I could even get the effect, it's called an anaglyph.
If I could even get that effect in OBS,
which it kind of worked.
I think it kind of worked, but it was a little difficult.
I think if I could perfect it, then it would work.
But, yeah, I was thinking maybe we can ask Crunchyroll
if we could hand out.
I think it was like 2,000 people in the panel hall.
If we could hand out like blue and red,
those paper 3D glasses, and then print it on it,
something like the Amish, Amish panel or something.
I feel like it's a cool thing to take home.
You know, you just have it, and it's like a memorabilia thing.
But I think it was too last minute anyways.
Well, I don't know, maybe they would have been it.
I don't even know how that would be possible.
I know you can rent 3D glasses.
You can rent like the polarized 3D glasses,
but those work differently.
It's like it takes...
Hmm.
I kind of understand how those like regular black frame 3D glasses work.
It like polarizes light circularly.
And so what it is, is like when you're watching
one of those 3D movies in theaters,
is they have like two projectors going,
or one that switches really fast back and forth,
and they're polarized.
Circularly polarized in opposite directions,
and each lens only allows one directional,
one direction of light, of the polarized light coming through.
I think I get it.
Yeah, but I couldn't figure out.
Obviously, I don't think it's possible with like computer monitors and stuff.
Unless we had a special projector.
It's magic! Yeah, it's magic.
How do they work?
Um...
Okay, yeah, light wave physics.
It was interesting watching.
I was like, oh, I just wanted a 3D stream,
but this is like pretty complicated.
They like talking about, you know, the light waves
and how they're electrically magnetized and whatever.
And I'm just like, okay, I get this, I get it.
I don't even think I took a physics class.
Oh, no.
I kind of took a physics class, yeah.
Oh, but I got it in the end, I got it.
Two YouTube tutorials later.
How do magnets work?
I don't know, how do they work?
It's magic.
Um...
Let's see.
Where was I?
Uh, George dedicated to me, thank you.
Yeah, I think, well, my manager was like,
I'm glad you liked the meeting group because, you know,
I guess it sort of implied there might be something else
coming up soon, so I don't know.
I think if there's some other conventions coming up soon,
it's possible that Halef might make an appearance,
but I'm not sure yet.
Uh, no confirmations yet.
Uh, Vercatos, thank you.
Oh, yeah, the top ten favorite anime.
My memory's so bad, like, I couldn't even remember
some of the anime that I really liked.
So I just put, like, a anime that I knew that I liked
and that I remembered that I liked,
but I think there's some anime that I really liked too
that I didn't remember to put on the list, if that makes sense.
Uh, can I say I'm saying kyuuu?
Congratulations!
A marriage, whoa!
Nice, thank you for the support.
I hope they have a successful marriage.
Marriage.
SS109, thank you.
Picoric, thank you.
Did you really see the Fortnite Battle Bus in real life?
Yes, I have seen the Fortnite Battle Bus in real life.
It was not a joke, I've actually seen it.
Um...
Amidoko kamsamita!
Ah, come on way up.
Fates, thank you.
Yo, yo, yo.
I'm reading Super Chats from this stream, by the way.
Amazing sand, thank you.
Yeah, I don't know if we'll do the same thing
for next year's Crunchyroll convention,
but it did seem like a lot of fun,
especially I just tweeted something before the stream.
Everybody's like, ame, ame.
And a small ame is there, I was there dancing.
A small ame was there dancing.
Uh, yeah, it seems like fun though.
Um, Mephi, thank you.
It doesn't have to be, you know,
only if your whole life fan is doing general, general anime stuff.
Um...
Um, Mephi, thank you.
Super Sunday time.
Stratus fight, thank you.
Immediates, thank you.
Bus, thank you.
You can get a degree at the panel the other day.
Thanks so well.
How different was it singing
and being able to watch the crowd?
Uh, I don't think I was watching the crowd during the...
Uh, yeah, when I was singing during my portion,
I wasn't watching the crowd
because I was looking at the lyrics.
But, um, yeah, like I said,
watching the crowd during Kura was really cool too.
Mm-hmm.
And Smart Boy, thank you.
Yeah, you'd think I'd memorize the lyrics too.
Puru put it in at this point.
But you just don't know.
I just wanted to make sure I got it right.
Yeah, I'd love to see you guys at more conventions.
That'd be cool.
Uh, EricW1, thank you.
Tried making amine last night.
It tasted pretty good.
Oh, nice. It wasn't too sweet.
I'm glad you liked it.
Video mote, thank you for the best of the chat.
Aww.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you for the question.
I'm glad you enjoyed the panel.
I-R-L.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'm done.
Yesterday, I got something to do.
This song sounds...
This song sounds kind of sad.
But, uh, it sounds like it's picking up a bit.
Alpha 9 5 7 1.
Ooh.
Cool.
Alpha 9 5 7 1, thank you.
Yeah, I hope you guys can make it to a mid-grade 2 coming soon near you.
Thank you.
Aww, thank you.
I'm glad you enjoyed.
Wait.
Thank you.
I'll see you laughing.
Ask Pei.
Thank you.
Are you able to upload some animated emotes to Twitch someday?
Maybe, perhaps?
Uh, I think it's an affiliate.
I don't remember if there were that many slots for it, but I'll look into it.
Yeah, I wanted to add a subscribers badge for Twitch, too.
So, I'll, uh, get started on that.
Mm-hmm.
Ifmefa, thank you.
Oh.
Aww, thank you.
Hola, Aime te quiero mucho.
Esta ludos desde Chile.
Oh, Chile.
Very chill.
Muchas gracias.
Anti-whippy, thank you.
It sometimes feels really for you that small Aime has broken out something so big.
She even became Ian's old mascot.
You envision her coming this far when you first brought her to be somewhat irregular?
Oh.
Well, yeah, small Aime is really popular.
I'm kind of nervous that, like, maybe I'm not doing enough on social media, you know, being small Aime.
So, I'm still trying to figure out what I can do to be better and be a better small Aime.
You know, because I'm small Aime's manager, actually, and I have to represent small Aime.
So, yeah.
But, yeah, it is really crazy.
It is surprising.
But, small Aime did have, like, a lot of memes when we started putting out, like, a lot of small Aime gifts and stuff,
and people started using them in memes.
So, I feel like small Aime has evolved, you know.
She's, like, 40 now.
Small Aime is the real idol here.
Maybe we should have a small Aime concert.
What do you guys think?
Oh, there's an idea.
Hey, I can do it on my own.
Well, not all alone, but...
Huh.
All right, well, stay tuned.
Flynn Playmable, thank you.
Oh, thank you. Yeah, that was sweet.
TK, thank you.
First, Akka Super Chat.
Oh, that was a solid one.
Thank you so much, TK.
Aw, thank you so much for the support. I appreciate it.
Princess Niche, thank you for the big support chat.
Thank you.
At TotoCubes, thank you.
Have I got a chance to go to an expo one day?
Yeah, now that things are opening up a little bit more.
Me too.
Last time, 39. Thank you.
The birthday shirt merch just arrived recently.
It looks so good.
Oh, yeah. It is unfortunate there's only one size.
Hmm, but you can always hang it up or something, you know?
Yeah, a lot of teammates that came to the...
Well, a few teammates that came to the meet-and-greet were wearing the Ame shirt.
Right next, thank you.
Does Mama get put back in the box?
Uh, yeah, she probably finally got apprehended again.
I know she's probably infected or something, so she's got to stay in the box, you know?
At TK, thank you.
Oh, thank you for that. Oh, another big sub-jet.
Aw.
Aw, thank you so much. That's so sweet.
I'm glad you enjoyed the streams.
Thank you, thank you for the support.
Thank you.
Rock the gas bar. Rock the gas bar.
I'm in it all night.
Rock the gas bar. Rock the...
Lock the taskbar.
All right, dear. Thank you.
Yeah.
It was pretty tough keeping small. I'm in check, but, uh...
You know, I think she's getting better.
I think she's improving a little bit.
Uh, Lynn, thank you.
YouTube has been recommending me saltwater tank videos.
There's this guy that bought $2,000 worth of fish, et cetera,
and even has a shark egg.
Yeah, there's so many of those videos on YouTube that's like,
fish haul, I just bought $5,000 worth of fish.
Watch me put them in.
And then it's like the guy opening up the video, and he's like,
what's up, fish heads?
And then he, like, talks for 10 minutes, and then finally unboxes the fish.
And it's not even that cool when you see it.
I do, though, I do on YouTube watch, uh...
They're, like, these two-hour compilations of people with, like,
really high-quality videos of their tanks.
And they do, like, really close-up, like, macro shots,
and there's, like, relaxing music, so...
That's, like, a good thing to put on in the background.
Uh, Kram, thank you so much!
Another big substitute!
It just says,
I'm in!
Thank you so much for the support.
TK, the third big super check!
Thank you so much!
Huh?
Aww, thank you, TK.
So sweet!
I see another one here, but TK, again.
Here, look, he's always so fun.
Game streams, always entertaining.
Chatty watch a lot of the super chat,
but his stream is so comfy,
and video stream projects always spark excitement.
Aww, thank you, thank you, thank you!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
So sweet!
Thank you so much!
I really appreciate it.
I'm glad, uh, you know,
at the end of the day,
if you guys enjoyed the stream somewhat,
I'm happy, so thank you.
And Majin D, thank you!
Majin 8, thank you!
I'll see you in the bar!
Traveling home from Crenshaw Expo,
I hope you get there safe.
I hope you win the lottery one day for the...
not just the regular lottery,
the main green lottery, I guess.
Uh, right here!
Thank you!
Endless Ame!
Only around Halloween.
Rock the guest box!
Ame, nee, nee, nee, nee, nee, nee!
Uh, Roger Liao, thank you!
Ame, ame, ame, ame, ame!
A12 Flames.
Thank you!
Oh!
Oh, the deep skies nuts!
Yeah, that was a tweet that I read during the panel.
Thank you for the question!
Uh, Mass Man Today, thank you!
Oh my god, this song is really loud.
Okay.
Okay, just the piano was really loud at the start.
Uh, where was I?
Oh, Mass Man Today, thank you!
Small minute at large, at Crenshaw Expo.
Uh-huh.
Uh, GK, thank you for another big supper chat!
Oh!
Uh, thank you so much!
Thank you!
I hope you also have a yummy food!
Mm-hmm!
Thank you so much for all the support.
I appreciate it.
Nagi!
Oh, thank you!
Mason Experience Music Meeting at Crenshaw Expo!
Oh, it was really sweet!
Thank you so much!
Nagi's so cute!
So cute!
Yeah, we got some pictures together.
Thank you, thank you for all your support.
I'm glad, uh, I'm glad you're able to make it to the convention and into the meeting greet.
Thank you!
So many cute teammates!
Uh, oh yeah, the figures that were posted, is the pop-up parade ones.
Did I have any input for the figure?
Uh, I think I had the option to provide, like, a reference that I might need to want something similar for the pose for the figure,
but I decided to leave it up to Navi Mama, so thank you, Navi Mama, for my adorable figure pose.
I think it was for that one.
Mm-hmm.
Aaron Pampo, thank you!
Happy birthday!
This year my sister made me an am statue, this year she made me custom am keep caps.
Ooh, an am party!
Dang, am cake!
Am day!
No, just kidding.
I hope the cake was tasty.
I mean, if it had me on it, it was definitely pretty tasty.
Aw, well thank you, happy birthday!
I hope you have a good rest of the day.
Night!
Yeah, custom keycaps, keycaps, cake?
Am cake?
Mm-hmm, am party!
Very cool.
A flag armor, thank you!
I'll be out of blackberries!
No, no, they're still on the...
They left them on the counter, they're still there!
Eduardo, thank you!
Uh, hi, Am, in your interview you mentioned that songs are coming soon.
Did you mean the cover with Navi or can we expect another one soon?
Did I say that?
Oh...
I don't remember.
Uh...
Yes, just assume that...
Yes, uh-huh.
I could be at 9-9, thank you!
Um, many times, thank you!
Yeah, you should try to go, it's a cool going to convention,
because, you know, the people around you,
if you start a conversation with them, which I know is scary,
but more than likely they'll know whatever it is you're talking to them about,
at least have heard of it.
Because, you know, it's like an anime convention,
so if you talk about anime or games, you know, you got something to bond over.
Mm-hmm!
Xinyoung-ho!
Thank you!
Uh, Seo-chan, thank you!
Since you're getting busier lately, do you still, uh,
aim for 22 games in 2022?
How many do I need left?
How many left are there that I need to complete?
I think it's possible, what?
How many months?
We still have 5 months.
I think it's possible.
20 more to go! 19?
Well, I have some shorter games.
Well, when I say shorter, I mean like 10-hour type of games,
that I think we could do.
But yeah, when I'm feeling better, I want to get to that,
and finish, I still have to finish, I want to finish Mafia,
Anion Y, and Mario Galaxy, as I almost said Mario Kart.
I'm gonna beat Mario Kart.
And I know, um,
there's one I've been keeping on the back burner,
but Frog Detective 3 is gonna come out,
and Katana Zero, uh, I still want to play at some point,
and, um, I don't know, I kind of feel like playing,
like a platform or something, like a 2D.
Ooh, I did want to play, um...
Hey!
What was that one game?
I almost said Banjo-Kazooie.
Uh...
Crash Bandicoot!
Yeah, I'm gonna play.
Stray? I don't know, it looks...
It looks cute, but I don't know.
Dun-dun-dun-dun-dun.
Hang-on Country 2, is that on the...
Switch?
Yeah, I don't know if I read that at some point,
I don't think, I don't know if I can finish it though,
it seems like a game that would take me a while.
Uh...
It is?
Dragon Country 2 would be the first one, didn't we?
We'll see.
Uh, Multi, thank you.
Aww...
Yeah, you gotta eat healthy so you have energy and stuff.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, EricW1, thank you.
Yeah, I think there will be another opportunity
to go to Expo and get, do the meet and greet and stuff.
Mm-hmm.
Anyways, thank you.
Don't skip lunch? Yeah, I should have lunch.
I'll take a break here before the next game that we play.
Have a snack.
Maybe I'll make a sandwich.
Uh, Marcela Botero, thank you.
Um, what do you mean, what?
Huh?
Go to start, thank you.
Aww, thank you, I'm glad you enjoyed the acapella pudurin.
Agent Quirobo, thank you.
Gracias.
Oh, Lord Turnip, thank you.
Would there be a post for the schedule this week?
Mm, I don't know, it's still debating.
I still haven't finished it, so I'm not sure yet.
Mm-hmm.
I think I will post something.
I don't know yet.
If not, then I will post the streams pretty early,
like 24 hours before.
Hopefully, yes, not hopefully, I will, if there's no schedule.
Mm-hmm.
Semen 2016, oh, thank you.
I hope you're having a good day too.
Niko Sek, oh, thank you, I'm glad you enjoyed
the Eurotruck sim stream.
You mean?
Yasami-ka!
Thank you.
Antipi, thank you.
Uploading Twitch VOD for YouTube during breakdays
might be a good way to help fill out the week.
Possibly.
That is true.
Oh, Yakitum44, thank you.
I gotta make the Twitch thumbnail.
I keep forgetting.
Yes, I'll make a thumbnail.
It'll be like a Twitch playlist of streams
that I've done on there, and I will upload them there
for archive reasons.
Archival, is that a word?
Uh...
Kirti, uh, Kirti, Kirti?
No, Bart, thank you.
Where's Super Chat?
Sorry, we do pops here.
I wonder if that's one of those names, or if you say it
like a, say something bad or something.
Motherfuckin' Rockas, thank you.
Twitch sucks!
Yeah, well, I think it's from a business perspective
good to stream every now and then.
Okay, like imagine this.
Let's say there's a collab that has three people streaming,
and all three of us are streaming on YouTube.
Okay, we're all streaming to the same audience.
Now, of course there's discoverability,
you know, possible within YouTube,
and that's great because a lot of our, obviously,
our whole audience is on YouTube.
But if you wanna open up to a different audience, okay,
a new people that maybe don't watch Hololive that often,
okay, you could have one person
streaming their perspective on Twitch,
and then you get even more people interested in Hololive.
That's business, baby!
But yeah, I think it's, I don't really mind streaming
like wherever, if it's YouTube or Twitch,
it's like the same, although when I do stream on Twitch,
I do feel like there's more of a possibility of new people.
I don't know.
Maybe it's just all in my head.
I gotta check the statistics.
Yeah, we'll stream on Vimeo.
How about that?
What was the other one?
Video motion.
Thank you.
Oh, gracias.
The motherfucking workers, thank you.
Nanji Misa, arigato.
Ame-chan, kawaii.
Thank you.
Arigato.
Shadowfire, thank you.
Oh, muchas gracias.
Nice.
Ellen Saputro.
Thank you.
Oh, Arowanas.
Yeah, they look cool.
I like them when they're small, when they're babies,
but Arowana is a type of fish.
They get big.
They get really big, and they'll bite you,
and you can bleed and stuff.
It's kind of scary, but yeah, you need a really big tank
for them, because they get up to a foot or longer.
Boi-boo, boi-boo.
They're so cute when they're small,
because their eyes are really big.
Let me see if I can show a picture.
Whoa, what is this?
They have this sack.
A weird sack.
What is this weird sack that they have?
I'll show you this picture.
Oh, see, they're so cute.
Yeah, they're expensive.
See, they have this little weird sack.
Is it like umbilical cord or something, but for fish?
Because it looks like only the babies have them.
What is that?
They're born with it?
A digestion sack?
Yeah, they get really big, though.
Let's see, fully grown.
Here.
Okay, this is like a YouTube thumbnail.
This is good for perspective.
I don't know who that is,
but now you can see perspective, like there's hand compared.
Wait, this looks like Photoshop.
No, it's not real.
It's a clickbait image.
They're not that big.
Let's see if I can find a better picture.
Okay, this is a good one.
Bim, bam, bim, bam.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're cute.
Cute, cute.
Omega hot dog.
Thank you.
What do you call an omega that makes gluten-filled bread?
A Watsonburg dishes baking bed.
Ha, ha.
Very funny.
Oh, Julia, thank you.
What?
Halfway.
Thank you.
You done?
I saw a small omelet at this event.
I didn't say we gave her a weapon, but didn't take it away.
Yago was also there.
Didn't do anything to him, right?
Well, have you seen Yago since yesterday?
Or since earlier today?
Suss.
Maka, thank you.
This is a big super chat.
If you don't remember backstaters,
don't feel forced to play with what you don't want.
Let me see.
Grindings like neon white.
Hmm?
Yeah, we'll see.
I just feel like for people watching,
maybe it's like repetitive or something.
I do think it is pretty fun, though.
I don't really mind backstating neon white
because I don't even look at chat
unless I ask you guys a question.
I'm sorry, boy.
Thank you.
Ryan, Quebec.
That's right.
Investigators.
No bathroom breaks.
Investigator breaks only.
Investigator meetings only.
A look-in.
Thank you.
Huh?
Okay.
Face of motion.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Bubble bot.
MVP.
Oh, what's it, Mila 5?
Oh, 1527.
Oh, thank you.
Yes, I'll pick them up.
Thank you.
Lucky senpai.
Oh, at the meet and greet.
Thank you for stopping by.
Thank you for the super chat.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Itsu-mo.
Kamalaya.
Is it itsu-mo?
Is it like it always...
It means like it's always or something?
Always.
AirW1, thank you.
Did you hear about the brawl at the restaurant?
Three fish got battered.
Oh, what does Bime use to style her hair at honeycomb?
Oh, I like that one.
That's a good one.
Okay, P-back.
I see.
Okay.
Hi, Gavin Dorff.
Thank you.
I just went to aquarium on vacation and saw Moray eel.
What's your favorite fish at the aquarium?
I always loved seeing the seahorses and then those fish that are closely related to seahorses.
Like, I forgot what they're called, but they're like dragon fish or something like that.
Something like that?
Oh, what are they called?
Dragon?
Dragon days?
No.
Sea dragons.
Yeah, sea dragons.
And also, those little fish that stick up from the sand.
Pipefish, I think?
They're so cute.
Oh, garden eels.
Yeah, I like seeing those types.
Seahorses especially.
You can keep seahorses as a pet, but I don't think I'm experienced enough as a saltwater
person because I saw one video of this guy and he had seahorses and one of his seahorses
had gas trapped inside of its stomach because, you know, the male seahorses hold baby seahorses
in like a womb where it's like a lot of tissue and stuff and what happens is that after they
give birth, after the baby seahorses leave the stomach, there could be leftover tissue
inside and over time it can start to rot and produce gas and so when there's gas in the
tummy, the seahorse can't swim properly.
It's like on its side and obviously it can die like that.
So the guy who owned the seahorse, you know, was part of his hobby, he had to take the
seahorse out and hold it in his hand and then take like a needle and stab like into like
where the babies come out and like just kind of stab the right place so that the gas expels
so that the seahorse can swim normally again.
So I don't know, I don't think I'd want to have a seahorse because that sounds really scary
to do.
And yeah, he took video of it and stuff and I don't think I could do that.
Yeah, you have to relieve the gas.
Those cows have something like that too because I've seen a video of like a cow where they
like poke something into its tummy and then its tummy like deflates because it had like
a build up of gas.
Yeah, yeah, they become buoyant and stuff, it's not good for them.
Mm-hmm.
It's scary.
What does that happen to us?
Maybe it does.
All right.
Hello, thank you.
Ah, Kenny Stamps, thank you.
Yeah, thank you.
Happy early international cat day to Wellington Henry.
Oh cute, what is that?
International cat day tomorrow?
There's too many, there's too many of these like weird holidays, internet holidays.
Oh my gosh.
What is that, international cat day tomorrow, there's too many of these like weird holidays,
internet holidays.
I'll make sure to give them a treat though.
Epic work, thank you.
Smalmed, we'll take over the world.
That'll one, thank you.
Can I hire Smalmed to come to my birthday party?
That'd be funny.
I'll keep them as a backup plan, yes.
I'll tell Smalmed that could be a good backup plan.
A Vtuber fan, thank you.
Oh, shout out to, I don't know about that, but I really appreciate all the support to
a Vtuber fan, thank you.
Thank you.
You're my main inspiration for becoming a Vtuber, I hope that one day we could collab,
even though the odds are probably super low.
Well, good luck.
It's good to have goals.
Sweet.
Cool, I hope it works out.
For a Kuma Forever one, thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
Many times, thank you.
Yeah, right.
I don't mind talking to Bubba, because they're just like, Bubba, you're so cute.
Bubba, you look so handsome today.
Bubba, who's a good boy?
Thank you.
It's fun to watch you go for times.
Oh, and the sunlight.
Thank you.
Well, we'll see.
We'll see this week, maybe.
Vek, thank you.
A red arrow one now.
All right, let's show the class.
Red arrow one now.
Oh, this looks like a fish who could catch an animal crossing.
Oh, I forgot this image was up here.
Mmm, pretty.
It looks like a big betta fish.
Yeah, very bright colored.
Cute.
They're chunky.
Very chunky.
This is a caption on this one.
It's transporting a rare arrow one.
You can see how big it is compared to the arms.
Yeah, they probably need like, what, 300 gallon tanks or something.
300 or more.
Hot Cheeto fish.
Yeah, it does kind of look like a hot Cheeto.
Okay, stamps.
This is the last Super Chat.
Don't send it anymore.
If you do, just know that I'm not going to read it.
This is the last Super Chat.
Can I say, thanks so much.
I'm glad you enjoyed Super Sundays,
even though they're not as long as they used to be,
but we get a nice condensed version.
And we have time for other stuff later.
All right, well, you guys have six minutes.
Let me go open up steam.
Uh-huh.
Four titties.
Titties.
30 bucks.
I'll make it back.
Wait, should I get Cities Skyline Deluxe Edition?
Because with the Deluxe, it comes with transit and industries.
And Harbor means $10 more.
Get the Deluxe.
All right.
Fine.
All right, I'll wait to buy it after I end this stream
because I'm paranoid.
Okay, it's in the cards, though.
All right, well, anything you guys want to tell me?
Oh, my God, there's only four more minutes left in the stream.
Oh, my God.
Swimsuit wallpaper.
I'm starting to inform you that members-only wallpaper,
which is coming soon, is not a swimsuit-themed one.
But I'll keep that in the Idea Bank.
Oh, no, I'm a doko.
Oh, yeah, the Crunchroll panel.
Yeah, that went well, right?
Yes, yes, the stream is done, but I'll be back in an hour.
I'm going to take a break.
I'm going to clean up an area where I made a mess.
And then I'm going to have a snack.
And then I have to install Cities Skyline, so yes.
Oh, just in time.
Let me pull up the lyrics so I can learn them better.
So fast.
Okay, okay.
It's hard to follow along. It's so fast.
So fast.
Thank you guys for watching.
I will see you in an hour.
My PC is so hot.
Okay.
Bye.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
We didn't reach the two hour mark yet.
Hold on. Hold on.
I'm still going.
So fast.